contentclick.co.uk 2015-06-07

# None

Information Use by ContentClick

ContentClick collects user submitted information such as name, email and password data to authenticate users, authenticate its commercial users, (ContentClick accounts and account services are available only to advertisers; they are not available to consumers), and to send notifications to those users relating to the ContentClick service. This information is not shared to anyone and is used by ContentClick so we can customize your experience and protect the security of your account.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding ContentClick’s services.

ContentClick logs IP address, date/time stamp, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to ContentClick’s account holders. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes

Cookies  
We may use cookies when you use our services. In addition, ContentClick uses cookies in connection with consumers visiting the web pages of social media sites where we provide services to our account holders; however, the data we collect in connection with consumers is used solely for tracking clicks and conversions – and is not used for any cross-site data collection or tracking. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by our servers to identify your computer to our servers. You can also disable cookies or otherwise manage them through tools provided with your browser software and with third-party software packages, or not use the features that require cookies. .

Links  
ContentClick and its services may link to other Applications and may link to other sites. ContentClick is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on or in connection with applications or websites controlled by third parties. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on ContentClick.

Consumer Data  
ContentClick does not collect personally identifiable information about consumers using the services which ContentClick provides to its commercial users. In particular, ContentClick does not collect or retain the following consumer information: name, race, religion, sexual orientation, health, social security number (or other government issued identifying number), insurance plan number, financial account number, information relaying precise, real-time location data (eg, through GPS or other location-based services), or information about past, present or future health or medical condition. Occasionally, ContentClick may receive consumer information, such as email addresses, from its advertising clients in connection with specific advertising campaigns. 

Security  
ContentClick user accounts are secured by user-created passwords and ContentClick takes certain precautions to insure that user account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect user information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the absolute security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on ContentClick, please contact us a [privacy@ContentClick.co.uk](mailto:privacy@adparlor.com)

Sharing and Disclosure of Information ContentClick Collects  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, ContentClick will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by ContentClick, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the ContentClick Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service.

Business Transfer  
ContentClick reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of ContentClick or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

Changes in Our Privacy Policy  
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

Memberships, Comments and Contacting the Web Site  
ContentClick is a wholly-owned subsidiary of digitalbox ltd., which is a member of the Direct Marketing Association, If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: privacy@ContentClick.co.uk or at:

ContentClick  
15 Gay Street   
Bath  
BA1 2PH
